openauto.com 2016-11-07

# New Car Dealer Prices | New Car Invoice Prices | New car Dealerships - OpenAuto.com USA

|   
---  
  
1\. INTRODUCTION.  
  
Reply!, Inc. d/b/a OpenAuto.com_(“us,” “we,” “our” or “Company”) is committed to respecting the privacy rights of its customers, visitors, and other users of the Company Website (“the Site”). We created this Website Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) to give you confidence as you visit and use the Site, and to demonstrate our commitment to fair information practices and the protection of privacy. This Privacy Policy is only applicable to the Site, and not to any other websites that you may be able to access from the Site, each of which may have data collection, storage, and use practices and policies that differ materially from this Privacy Policy. Use of our Site and the services herein, and any disputes arising from it, is subject to this Privacy Policy as well as the Site’s Terms of Use and all of its dispute resolution provisions, including arbitration, limitation on damages and choice of law.  
  
2\. INFORMATION COLLECTION PRACTICES.  
  
2.1. TYPES OF INFORMATION COLLECTED  
  
(a) TRAFFIC DATA COLLECTED. We automatically track and collect the following categories of information when you visit our Site: (1) IP addresses; (2) domain servers; (3) types of computers accessing the Site; and (4) types of web browsers used to access the Site (collectively “Traffic Data”). Traffic Data is anonymous information that does not personally identify you but is helpful for marketing purposes or for improving your experience on the Site. We or our third party partners may also use “cookies” to customize content specific to your interests, to ensure that you do not see the same advertisement repeatedly, and to store your password so you do not have to re-enter it each time you visit the Site.   
  
(b) PERSONAL INFORMATION COLLECTED. In order for you to access certain premium services and/or to receive quotes and information that we offer via the Site, we may require you to provide us with certain information that personally identifies you (“Personal Information”). Personal Information includes the following categories of information: (1) Contact Data (such as your name, mailing address, phone number (including mobile) and e-mail address); (2) Financial Data (such as your account or credit card number); (3) Personal Data (such as your Social Security Number); and (4) Demographic Data (such as your zip code, age, interests and income). If you communicate with us by e-mail, post messages to any of our chat groups, bulletin boards, or forums, or otherwise complete online forms, surveys, or contest entries, any information provided in such communication may be collected as Personal Information. Also note that we may collect and store information that you provide to us about other people (such as co-borrowers), including their name, address, telephone number, mobile devices, email address and Social Security Number; such information will be afforded the same treatment as Personal Information.   
  
2.2. USES OF INFORMATION COLLECTED  
  
(a) COMPANY USE OF INFORMATION. We use Contact Data for the purpose for which it was collected, as disclosed at the time such Contact Data is provided to us, to send you information about our Company or our Company’s products or services, or promotional material from some of our partners, or to contact you when necessary. We use your Financial Data and Personal Data to verify your qualifications for certain products or services and, where applicable, to bill you for products and services. We use your Demographic Data to customize and tailor both yours and other consumers experience on the Site, displaying content that we think you or other consumers might be interested in and according to your preferences. We also use Demographic Data to remarket products and services that may be of interest to you.   
  
(b) SHARING OF PERSONAL INFORMATION. We share your Personal Information with our trusted partners, advertisers, service providers, affiliates, and other third parties that we believe can provide you with information or support related to your online inquiry or with additional special offers and opportunities. We share Demographic Data with advertisers and other third parties on an aggregate (i.e., non-personally-identifiable) basis. We share Contact Data, Financial Data and Personal Data with other companies who provide products or services requested by you or who may want to send you information about their products or services, unless you have specifically requested that we not share Contact Data with such companies. We also share Contact Data and Financial Data with our business partners who assist us by performing core services (such as hosting, billing, fulfillment, or data storage and security) related to our operation of the Site. We screen third parties with whom Personal Information is shared and, while many of our partners have agreed to uphold the same standards of security and confidentiality contained in this Privacy Policy, we make no guarantee about third parties use and protection of your Personal Information or their willingness to abide by our Privacy Policy. If you do not want us to share your Personal Information with any third parties, please email us at legal@buyerlink.com or send a written communication to 3000F Danville Blvd. #151, Alamo, CA 94507. Please understand that such a request will likely limit your ability to take advantage of all of the features and services we offer on the Site.   
  
(c) USER CHOICE REGARDING COLLECTION, USE, AND DISTRIBUTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION. You may choose not to provide us with any Personal Information. In such an event, you can still access and use much of the Site; however you will not be able to access and use those portions of the Site that require your Personal Information. If you do not wish to receive information and promotional material from us or from some of our partners, you may follow the instructions provided in Section 2.2(b) above.   
  
3\. CONFIDENTIALITY AND SECURITY OF PERSONAL INFORMATION.  
  
Except as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy, we will keep your Personal Information private and will not share it with third parties, unless such disclosure is necessary to: (a) comply with a court order or other legal process; (b) protect our rights or property; or (c) enforce our Terms of Use. Your Personal Information is stored on secure servers that are not accessible by third parties. We provide you with the capability to transmit your Personal Information via secured and encrypted channels if you use a similarly equipped web browser.  
  
4\. PUBLIC INFORMATION.  
  
The Site contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. We may also make chat rooms, forums, message boards, and news groups available to you. Please understand that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information. We have no control over its use and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your Personal Information.   
  
5\. UPDATES AND CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY.  
  
We reserve the right, at any time and without notice, to add to, change, update, or modify this Privacy Policy, simply by posting such change, update, or modification on the Site and without any other notice to you. Any such change, update, or modification will be effective immediately upon posting on the Site.  
  
6\. ASSIGNMENT.  
  
In our sole discretion, we may transfer, sell or assign your Personal Information collected on and through this website to one or more third parties, as a result of the sale, merger, consolidation, change in control, transfer of substantial assets, reorganization or liquidation of OpenAuto.com and/or Reply!, Inc.   
  
7\. GOOGLE ANALYTICS ADVERTISING.  
  
We have enabled and use certain Google Analytics Advertising Features, including, but not limited to, Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting, on the Site. This enables us to collect data via Google advertising cookies and anonymous identifiers. We use the data to optimize our Site and for remarketing purposes. You may opt-out of the Google Analytics Advertising Features by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative Consumer Opt Out page found [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/).   
  
The Privacy Notice posted on this site was updated on August 25, 2014.
